Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
SCOTT:  Previously on
Teen Wolf...
You can't just
go around turning
people into werewolves.
I can if they're willing.
Scott, I'm trying
to break up with you.
It's okay, because I know
we're gonna be together.
DEREK:  It's their symbol.
And it means they're coming.
Who?
An Alpha pack.
And they're not coming.
They're already here.
(GROWLING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GROANING)
Quiet.
Stay with me.
We're almost there.
ISAAC: My neck.
GIRL: From their claws.
It's how they
share memories.
But I don't
remember anything.
Also how they steal them.
Listen to me,
no matter what happens
you hold on, okay?
You hold on tight.
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
I hear something.
Someone's coming.
Faster!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Two of them.
(HORN BLARES)
No!
Remember what
I said before?
Hold on?
Hold on!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
Whoa!
GIRL: Isaac?
Stay with me!
Isaac!
(GROWLING)
(ROARS)
GIRL: Isaac!
Get down!
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
I thought I told
you to hold on.
(POP MUSIC)
Boy, it's a good thing
you drew me a picture.
Hey, Scott,
sure you don't want
something like this?
Too soon?
Yeah.
I don't know, man,
are you sure about this?
I mean, these things
are pretty permanent,
you know?
I'm not changing my mind.
Okay, but why two bands?
I just like it.
But don't you think your
first tattoo should have
some sort of meaning,
you know, or something?
Getting a tattoo
means something.
I don't think that's...
TATTOO ARTIST: He's right.
Tattooing goes back
thousands of years.
The Tahitian word  "tatua"
means "to leave a mark."
Like a rite of passage.
Yeah, you see? He gets it.
He's covered in tattoos,
Scott, literally.
Okay, you ready?
(CLEARS THROAT)
You ain't got any problems
with needles, do you?
Nope.
(NEEDLE BUZZES)
I tend to get a little
squeamish though, so...
(NEEDLE BUZZES)
(MUMBLES)
Oh, man.
(GROANING)
You okay?
Kind of burns.
Yes, you just had
your skin stabbed
about 100,000
times with a needle.
Yeah, but I don't
think it's supposed
to feel like this.
(GROANS) Oh, God.
No, it's definitely not
supposed to feel like this.
I gotta take
this thing off.
No, no, no, no, Scott.
Scott, please stop.
Whoa, whoa.
Oh, no, what?
No, no, come on.
It healed.
(EXHALES)
Thank God. I hated it.
Sorry.
LYDIA: It is not
a double date.
It is a group thing.
Do they know
it's a group thing?
'Cause I told you
that I'm not ready
to get back out there.
You were in France
and didn't do any dating
for four months?
Did you?
I mean, after...
Do not say his name.
Is he okay? I mean,
did everything work out?
Well, the doctors
looked like total idiots
when he turned up alive,
but everyone got over it.
And yes, Derek taught him
the werewolf 101,
like how not to
randomly kill people
during a full moon.
So then you've
talked to him?
Uh, not since
he left for London.
You mean since his dad
moved him to London.
Whatever, he left.
And seriously, an American
werewolf in London?
Like that's not
going to be a disaster.
So you're totally over him?
Would I be going on
a double date if I wasn't?
(CHUCKLES)
Yes, it is a double date.
It's not an orgy.
(CHUCKLES)
You'll live.
SCOTT: Nah, we agreed
to give each other
the summer.
No texts, no calls.
So then how do you know
she won't be
back at school then?
SCOTT: After everything
that happened,
I'm not sure she's
coming back at all.
I think she is.
I'd say pretty definite,
you know.
Like 100%.
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC)
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I can't see him, not now.
Can we just drive
please, Stiles?
Scott, it's a red light.
Lydia, go. Just go!
LYDIA: But the light.
STILES: I think
we should talk to her.
I just think we
should say something.
No. No, no,
Stiles, come on.
Oh, my God, dude, no.
Hey!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
You know,
they probably
didn't see us.
(SIGHS)
You all right?
What are you doing?
I'm driving.
We're right behind them.
Okay, well,
do you see any turns?
I don't want it
to look like
we're following them.
Well, what do you
want me to do?
I don't know, anything.
(TIRES SCREECH)
ALLISON: Lydia, stop.
We need to go back
and talk to them.
LYDIA: They stopped, too.
Why would they stop?
It's Stiles and Scott.
Do you really wanna
try applying logic
to those two?
Maybe we should go back.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Are you okay?
It came out of nowhere.
Are you hurt?
It ran right into us.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Well, I'm not okay.
(EXHALES) I am
totally freaking out.
How the hell does
it just run into us?
I saw its eyes
right before it hit us.
It was like it...
...it was like
it was crazy.
No, it was scared.
Actually, terrified.
MELISSA: Hey, wait.
Wait a minute.
I know this one.
What happened, Isaac?
Listen, the girl, all right,
she's worse, okay?
Are you not healing?
I will.
Will you just...
Would you just
help her, please?
Okay, can you take him?
We gotta move him,
Melissa.
All right, take him.
Hey. Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey.
Find him.
I have to find him.
What are you saying?
I have to...
I have to tell him.
Who?
The Alpha.
Find the Alpha.
What do you want
with Derek Hale?
No.
What?
MAN: Okay, let's
get her out of here.
Not Hale.
McCall.
Scott McCall.
(UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC)
(BEEP)
"Ephemeral."
Lasting for a short time.
"Transient. Momentary."
Ephemeral.
You ready?
Yeah.
You know, you could
wait till tomorrow
if you want.
I know the first
day can be tough.
I'm all right.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Or you could wait a week,
if that would
make things easier.
I promised Lydia
that I would drive her,
since her car's wrecked.
So I should go.
You know how many
vehicle collisions
last year involved deer?
247,000.
Oh, God,
please go to school.
But that's crossing the road.
This one last night came
right down the middle.
I'm not gonna beg you.
Okay, good. I'm impervious
to your influence anyway.
Would you consider a bribe?
You couldn't meet my price.
Extortion?
You got nothing on me.
Yeah.
Dad, what are you doing?
Aah!
(THUD)
(POP MUSIC)
Looks good on you.
So you think we could go
on a real date sometime?
Hmm...
Uh...
Can we have sex again?
Mmm.
You wanna ask
Derek for help?
Why? Why?
He's got the triskele
tattooed on his back.
So there has to be
a way to do it
without healing, right?
Okay, yeah, but still,
doesn't he have his
hands a little full?
PRINCIPAL: Look,
these are the applications
for the career advisor.
I need them sorted.
And whatever
happened to the library
while I was gone,
I want it cleared up.
And what the
hell is this?
Go. Go. Go.
LYDIA: Freshmen.
Tons and tons
of fresh men.
You mean fresh boys.
Lydia, they're 14.
Eh, some are more
mature than others.
ALLISON: You know,
it's okay to be single.
Focus on yourself
for a little while,
work on becoming
a better person.
(CHUCKLES)
Allison, I love you.
So if you need
to do that thing
where we talk about me
and pretend like
we're not actually
talking about you,
it's totally fine.
But I don't want
a boyfriend.
I want a distraction.
Brothers?
Twins.
(GASPS)
MELISSA: Yeah. Yeah,
that's healing, visibly.
Wow. They can't see this.
Nobody can see this.
All right,
cover it up.
I don't think
that's gonna matter.
I mean,
you're scheduled for surgery,
which is obviously
gonna be very confusing
for a lot of people.
Okay, can you do something?
Me do something?
I'm relatively new
to all of this.
And there's a sheriff's deputy
that's stationed
right outside the door.
Have you tried
calling Derek?
Like, five times.
Do you have any other
emergency werewolf contacts?
Yeah.
Call Scott.
STILINSKI:
Believe me, sir.
I understand.
But you have
to understand me.
Excuse me.
Hey, hey, Melissa.
Hey.
Can you help me out here?
Yeah.
Since the amnesiac in 215
can't tell us anything,
I need the girl
with the modified
military stun gun in 216
to answer
a few questions.
It's kind of unlikely,
since she's heavily sedated.
STILINSKI:
Ah, great. Um...
Well, when she un-sedates,
will you give me a call?
'Cause she's got
about $10,000 worth
of property damage
to answer for.
And I don't want her
just walking out of here.
MELISSA: Okay.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
Is someone...
No. No, no, no, no.
No, it's all you,
all yours.
It's totally vacant.
(PHONES VIBRATING, RINGING)
MS. BLAKE:
"The offing was barred
by a black bank of clouds
"and the tranquil waterway,
"leading to the uttermost
ends of the earth
flowed somber
"under an overcast sky,
"seemed to lead
into the heart of
an immense darkness."
This is the last line
to the first book
we are going to read.
It is also the last text
you will receive
in this class.
Phones off, everyone.
Oh, come on,
Scott, come on.
Oh, pick up.
Hello, Isaac.
Hi.
How we feeling?
Good. Listen,
I think I could
probably just...
What is that?
Just an anesthetic.
We don't want you getting
in the way again.
Count along with me, Isaac.
One. Two.
Three.
(DOOR OPENS)
(WHISPERING)
Mr. McCall?
Uh...
I'm sure it's an emergency
if your mother needs
you to leave school,
but I'm gonna
give you a warning
in the nicest possible way.
I am well aware of
your attendance record.
I don't wanna see you slip
back into old habits.
I won't.
It's gonna be
different this year.
Resolutions are only good
if you stick with them, Scott.
I will.
I promise it
won't be ephemeral.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROWLS)
(EXHALES)
Hey, Lydia.
What is that?
Is that from the accident?
No. Prada bit me.
Your dog?
No, my designer handbag.
Yes, my dog.
Has it ever
bitten you before?
Okay. What if it's, like,
the same thing as the deer?
You know, like,
how animals start acting weird
right before
an earthquake or something?
Meaning what? There's
gonna be an earthquake?
Or something.
Maybe it means
something's coming.
Something bad.
It was a deer and a dog.
What's that thing
you say about threes?
Once, twice...
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(GASPS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Get down, everyone!
Get down! Get down!
Get down!
Why didn't you
tell me before?
Honestly, I was hoping
I didn't have to.
What do you mean?
Everything that
you've been doing,
the extra reading,
the summer school,
saving up for the bike,
even though it scares me
half to death...
Honey, I just didn't wanna
disrupt a good rhythm.
It's not gonna stop.
I'm gonna be better
this year.
A better student,
a better son,
a better friend,
a better everything.
I promise.
Okay.
He's in room 215
if he isn't
already in surgery.
Okay. Thank you.
(SIGHS)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
(DUBSTEP MUSIC)
Would you hit the button
for the second floor, please?
Yeah.
Thank you.
DOCTOR:
What the hell is this?
Does someone want to
explain this to me?
You wouldn't mind
helping me out
for a second, would you?
Um...
Sure.
DOCTOR: Here's an idea.
Why don't you wheel
this joker out of here
and get somebody
that actually needs
to be operated on?
Now!
I'm gonna go smoke.
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(DUBSTEP MUSIC)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLS)
(GROWLS)
Don't you realize what
you're dealing with?
I'm an Alpha.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(GROWLS)
So am I.
(GRUNTS)
Aren't you supposed
to be in school?
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
Ms. Blake?
You okay?
Sorry, just... That.
Next time you're feeling
you wanna stay home,
you stay home.
I'm okay.
But, Dad, the deer
and now this?
I know. I know.
ALLISON: It can't
be a coincidence.
Mr. Argent, you wouldn't
have any insight into this,
would you?
Me?
Yeah.
All this bizarre
animal behavior, it's...
You must have seen something
like this before, right?
I'm not sure why I would
or why you would
think I would.
I'm sorry.
I could've sworn
I overheard my son
talking about how you were
an experienced hunter.
Ah, right.
Well, not anymore.
You all right?
Yeah.
STILES:  We got a serious
problem at school.
Ms. Blake's class...
Hey, can you tell
me about it later?
Well, no,
pretty sure this qualifies
for immediate discussion.
All right,
then meet me at Derek's.
Derek's house? What?
What the hell
are you doing at...
SCOTT: Just meet
us here, okay?
You don't still
live here, do you?
No.
The county took it over,
but there's something here
that I need.
It'll help heal a wound
from an Alpha.
Yeah, but it did heal.
Not on the inside.
Hey, are you gonna tell me
who that was back there?
That Alpha.
A rival pack.
It's my problem.
I know you wanna help,
and you did. I owe you one.
Now go home.
Go back to
being a teenager.
Hey, Derek.
If you wanna repay
back that favor now,
there is something
you can do for me.
Is it me or is Beacon Hills
turning into more like
beacon for
the totally bizarre
and supernatural?
Where's Scott McCall?
You're Allison, right?
Yeah, how do you know...
Where's Scott?
He had to leave.
He was supposed to
be back in class...
Is he coming back?
Hey.
Easy with the physicality,
sweetheart.
(DEEP BREATH)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(GRUNTS)
Well, she bruised me.
ALLISON: Huh. Me, too.
Come on, let's get you
two girls out of here.
School can wait
another day.
Sweetheart?
Hey.
You don't have to worry
about this anymore.
Remember our agreement?
We stay in Beacon Hills,
but only if we
stay out of this.
It's not our problem now.
Okay?
We've had 15 calls
in the past hour.
I got a suicidal deer,
birds flying through windows,
pets behaving aggressively.
I gotta tell you,
I'm starting to think
there's something
in the water.
To be honest,
I was gonna give you
a call about
an incident of my own.
At first,
I thought I might
have had a break-in.
Some sick individual
looking to release
a particularly
violent impulse.
Until I got a closer look
and realized what
actually happened.
They did it
to themselves.
Yeah, I see it.
It's two bands, right?
What does it mean?
I don't know.
It's just something
I traced with my fingers.
Why is this so
important to you?
Do you know
what the word
"tattoo" means?
To mark something.
Well, that's in Tahitian.
In Samoan,
it means "open wound."
I knew I wanted
to get a tattoo
when I turned 18.
I always wanted one.
I just decided to get it now,
to make it kind of a reward.
For what?
For not calling
or texting Allison all summer.
Even when I
really wanted to,
even when it was
so hard not to sometimes.
I was trying to give her
the space she wants.
(SIGHS)
Going four months later,
it still hurts.
It still feels like a...
Like an open wound.
Yeah.
The pain's gonna be worse
than anything
you've ever felt.
Ah, that's great.
Do it.
STILES: Oh, wow.
That's a lot for me.
So I'm gonna
take that as my cue.
I'm just gonna
wait outside.
Nope.
You can help hold him down.
Oh, my God.
(SCREAMS)
Hold him.
(GASPS)
It worked.
(PANTING)
Well, it looks pretty
damn permanent now.
Yeah.
I kind of needed
something permanent.
Everything that's
happened to us,
everything just
changes so fast.
Everything's so...
Ephemeral.
Studying for the PSATs?
Yep.
Nice.
You painted the door.
Why'd you paint the door?
Go home, Scott.
And why only
one side?
Scott.
(TENSE MUSIC)
(GRUNTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
The birds at school
and the deer last night,
just like the night
I got trampled
by the deer
when I got bit
by the Alpha.
How many are there?
(SIGHS) A pack of them.
An Alpha pack.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ROCK MUSIC)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
All of them?
How does that even work?
I hear there's
some kind of a leader.
He's called Deucalion.
(TENSE MUSIC)
We know they have
Boyd and Erica.
Peter, Isaac, and I have
been looking for them
for the last four months.
Let's say
you find them.
How do you deal
with an Alpha pack?
With all the help
I can get.
ISAAC: Where is she?
Where's the girl?
What girl?
(PANTING)
DEUCALION: Beautiful.
But defiant, aren't you?
Because I know something.
I know you're
afraid of him.
Of a teenage boy?
Of the man he'll become.
I'm aware of a certain
potential threat.
But then someone
once taught me
a very smart way
to eliminate threat.
Get someone else
to do it for you.
Derek.
(GROWLS)
This one,
it's perfect.
I don't know.
I'm still thinking
maybe a shade of blue.
(TENSE MUSIC)
Lydia, look.